<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet
      title="Create a new business rule analysis">
   <intro>
      <description>
         This kind of analysis allows you to apply your Business Rules to a selected table. 

Note that you can create Business Rules and assign them to the analysis created at a later stage of analysis preparation.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item
         title="Set the analysis metadata">
      <description>
         To open the <b>Create New Analysis</b> wizard, right click either the <b>Analyses</b> folder on the <b> DQ Repository</b> tree view and select <b>New Analysis</b>. Expand <b>Table Analysis</b> and select <b>Business Rule Analysis</b>(or click the link below). The wizard prompts you to provide the analysis metadata (name, purpose, description....). Browse to and select the table or view to analyze and then select the <b>Business Rules</b> to apply. Upon completion an editor opens, in which you can modify the metadata and review the analysis settings.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.CreateNewAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false" param1="11">
      </action>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Select tables or views to analyze">
      <description>
         Click <b>Select tables/views to analyze</b> in the editor (or click the link below). Browse to and select the table(s) or view(s) of interest. The tables or views selected appear in the <b>Analyzed Tables/Views</b> part of the editor.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.OpenColumnSelectorAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false" param1="11">
      </action>
   </item>
   <item
         skip="true"
         title="Add rules to the table">
      <description>
         To add a business rule to a table, click the <b>Business Rule</b> icon next to the name of the table you want to add a rule to. In the dialog box which opens, browse to and select the business rule of interest. Alternatively, drop a rule from the <b>DQ Repository</b> tree view on the left, next to the name of the table of interest.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Analyze.">
      <description>
         To execute the analysis, click the <b>Run</b> button located to the top left of the editor (or click the link below). You can also run an analysis from the <b>DQ Repository</b> tree view. To do so, right click the relevant analysis and click the <b>Run</b> icon on the contextual menu which appears.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.RunAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false"/>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
