<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet
      title="Create a new catalog overview analysis">
   <intro>
      <description>
         This type of analysis analyzes one specific catalog in a database and returns information about the catalog content.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item
         skip="false" dialog="true"
         title="Select a catalog to analyze">
      <description>
       Note that catalog analysis is only possible in databases in which catalog entities are part of their physical structure. To open the <b> Create New Analysis </b> wizard, right click the <b>Analyses</b> folder on the <b>DQ Repository</b> tree view and select <b>New Analysis</b>. Expand <b>Structural Analysis</b> and select <b>Catalog Overview Analysis</b>(or click the link below). The wizard prompts you to provide the analysis metadata (name, purpose, description....). Browse to and select a catalog to analyze, and add table or view filters if required. Upon completion an editor opens, in which you can review the analysis settings.
      </description>
    <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.CreateNewAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core"  param1="7" confirm="false"/>
   </item>
   <item
         skip="true"
         title="Review your settings">
      <description>
         You can review and modify your settings, if necessary, in the catalog editor. Click <b>Analysis Parameters</b> to modify the table or view filters in the corresponding fields.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Analyze">
      <description>
         To execute the analysis, click the <b>Run</b> icon located to the top left of the editor (or click the link below). You can also run an analysis from the Repository tree view. To do so, right click the relevant analysis and click the <b>Run</b> icon on the contextual menu which appears.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.RunAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false"/>
      
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
