<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Create a new column analysis">
   <intro>
      <description>
         This kind of analysis examines the content of a set of columns. 
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="Set the analysis metadata." dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         To open the <b>Create New Analysis</b> wizard, right click <b>Analyses</b> on the <b>DQ Repository</b> view and select <b>New Analysis</b>. Then select analysis under <b>Column Analysis</b> folder. Alternatively, browse to and click right on a column on the <b> DQ Repository </b> view tree and select <b>Analyze</b>. The wizard prompts you to provide the analysis metadata (name, purpose, description...). Upon completion, an editor opens in which you can modify the analysis metadata and define the analysis settings. 		 		
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.CreateNewAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false" param1="6">
      </action>
   </item>
   <item title="Select the columns to analyze." dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
          In the editor, click <b>Select Data</b> button(or <b>New Connection</b> first) under the <b>Data preview</b> section to open a dialog box in which you can browse to and select data to analyze. Alternatively, you can drop the columns from the <b>DQ Repository</b> tree view onto the <b>Analyzed Columns</b> box in the editor.
		 
Under <b>Data Mining Type</b>, define the type of the corresponding column. 		 
		 
Note: <b>Nominal</b> means that the column contains textual values (no order or mathematical function applicable). <b>Interval</b> means that mathematical functions (such as the average) can be used. average) can be used.</description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.OpenColumnSelectorAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false" param1="6">
      </action>
   </item>
   <item title="Select the indicators to compute." dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Click the <b>Select Indicators</b>  button under the <b>Data Preview</b> section to open the <b>Indicator Selection</b> dialog box. Apply the indicators required for each column by selecting the corresponding check boxes(or click the link below).iption>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.OpenIndicatorSelectorAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false">
      </action>
   </item>
   <item
         skip="true"
         title="Add a UDI">
      <description>
         Click the <b>UDI</b> button for each column you want to set the <b>User Defined Indicator</b> for. In the <b>UDI Selector</b> dialog box, select the check boxes which correspond to the indicators desired.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Set the indicator options." dialog="true" skip="true">
      <description>
         Click on the <b>options</b> icon next to each indicator you want to define the values for (or click the link below). By default, reasonable options are chosen.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         skip="true"
         title="Choose a pattern for each column">
      <description>
        For each column, you can add a pattern indicator. There are two kinds of patterns. Regular patterns are regular expressions (not supported by all databases) and SQL patterns are the patterns that you add in a &quot;LIKE&quot; clause. Click the <b>Add Pattern</b> button next to each column, then browse to and select the pattern you want to add in the dialog box which appears. Alternatively, drop a pattern from the <b>DQ Repository</b> tree view onto a column. 		 
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Set filters on the data to be analyzed." dialog="true" skip="true">
      <description>
This is an optional step. By default, all of the data is analyzed. 
To filter the data, write an SQL &quot;WHERE&quot; clause in the <b>Data Filter</b> text box.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Analyze." dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
		 Click the <b>Run</b> icon, located towards the top left of the editor, to execute the analysis. Alternatively, right click the analysis on the <b>DQ Repository</b> tree view and click the <b>Run</b> icon on the list which appears.	        
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.RunAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false">
      </action>
   </item>
   <item title="Refresh the graphics" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
To view the analysis graphics, click the <b>Refresh the graphics</b>  hyperlink (or click the link below). The graphics displayed will reflect the most recently computed data.        
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.RefreshChartAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false">
      </action>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
