<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet
      title="Create a new column set analysis">
   <intro>
      <description>
      This kind of analysis examines the content of a set of columns. The analysis returns the row count, distinct count, unique count and duplicate count.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item
         skip="false"
         title="Set the analysis metadata.">
      <description>
          To open the <b>Create New Analysis</b> wizard, right click <b>Analyses</b> on the <b>DQ Repository</b> view and select <b>New Analysis</b>. Then expand <b>Table Analysis</b> and select <b>Column Set Analysis</b>. The wizard prompts you to provide the analysis metadata (name, purpose, description...). Upon completion, an editor opens in which you can modify the analysis metadata and define the analysis settings. 		 		
      </description>
       <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.CreateNewAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false" param1="10">
      </action>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Select the columns to analyze.">
      <description>
        In the editor, click <b> Analyzed Columns</b> (or click the link below). Then click <b>Select columns to analyze</b> to open a dialog box in which you can browse to and select the columns to analyze. Alternatively, you can drop the columns from the <b>DQ Repository</b> tree view onto the <b>Analyzed Columns</b> box in the editor. 
		 
Under <b>Data Mining Type</b>, define the type of the corresponding column. 		 
		 
Note: <b>Nominal</b> means that the column contains textual values (no order or mathematical function applicable). <b>Interval</b> means that mathematical functions (such as the average) can be used.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.OpenColumnSelectorAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false" param1="10">
      </action>
   </item>
   <item
         skip="true"
         title="Set the indicator options.">
      <description>
         Click the <b>Options</b>  button next to each indicator you want to set parameters for. Then enter the higher and lower threshold values. By default, standard parameters are set.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         skip="true"
         title="Choose a pattern for each column">
      <description>
   		For each column, you can add a pattern indicator. There are two kinds of patterns. Regular patterns are regular expressions (not supported by all databases) and SQL patterns are the patterns that you add in a &quot;LIKE&quot; clause. Click the <b>Add Pattern</b> button next to each column, then browse to and select the pattern you want to add in the dialog box which appears. Alternatively, drop a pattern from the Repository view onto a column.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         skip="true"
         title="Set filters on the data to be analyzed.">
      <description>
	  This is an optional step. By default, all of the data is analyzed. 
To filter the data, write an SQL &quot;WHERE&quot; clause in the <b>Data Filter</b> text box.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Analyze.">
      <description>
		 Click the <b>Run</b> icon, located towards the top left of the editor, to execute the analysis. Alternatively, right click the analysis on the <b>DQ Repository</b> tree view and click the <b>Run</b> icon on the list which appears.	
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.RunAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false">
      </action>
   </item>
   <item
         skip="false"
         title="Refresh the graphics">
      <description>
         To view the analysis graphics, click the <b>Refresh the graphics</b>  hyperlink (or click the link below). <b>Refresh the graphics</b> means that the graphics displayed will reflect the most recent data computed.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.RefreshChartAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false">
      </action>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
