<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Create a new match analysis">
	<intro>
		<description>
			Match Analysis analyzes duplicates and similar records in a data set. It
			helps you define
			<b>Match Rules</b>
			that can be used in analyses or in match components.
		</description>
	</intro>
	<item title="Set the analysis metadata.">
		<description>
			To open the
			<b>Create New Analysis</b>
			wizard, right click
			<b>Analyses</b>
			in the
			<b>DQ Repository</b>
			tree view and select
			<b>New Analysis</b>
			. Type &quot;Match&quot; in the filter field, and then select
			<b>Match Analysis</b> from the analysis list.
			A wizard prompts you to provide the analysis metadata (name,
			purpose, description...). Upon completion, an editor opens in which
			you can modify the analysis metadata and define the analysis
			settings.
		</description>
		<action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.CreateNewAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false" param1="12">
        </action>
	</item>
	<item skip="true" title="Connect to a data source">
		<description>
			Create the
			<b>connection</b>
			to the data source you want to analyze. If you have already defined some metadata
			that you want to reuse, just skip this step.
			<br/>
			To create a metadata
			connection from within the editor, you can click on the
			<b>New Connection</b>
			button in the
			<b>Match Analysis</b>
			editor.
			<br/>
			You can also right-click on the subfolders of the
			<b>Metadata</b>
			folder in the
			<b>DQ Repository</b> tree view.
			In this step, you will be invited to select the columns to
			analyze.
		</description>
        <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.CreateNewConnectionForMatchAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core">
        </action>
	</item>

	<item skip="true" title="Select data to analyze">
		<description>
			If you have already selected the data to analyze in the previous step, you
			may skip this step.
			In the match editor, click the &quot;Select Data&quot;
			button. Then browse and select the columns to analyze.
			In the <b>Limit</b> field, set the number of the data records you want to use as a data sample on which to test the match rule.
		</description>
        <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.SelectDataForMatchAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core">
        </action>
	</item>

	<item title="Generate a blocking key">
		<description>
			Select the columns that will be used to generate a blocking key. A
			blocking key is required when you have a lot of data
			to analyze. In the <b>Data</b> view, click
			on the
			<b>Select Blocking Key</b>
			tab and click the column header in the data table. This will add the columns to the
			blocking key table. You need to click at 
			<b>Select Blocking Key</b>
			again to finish the selection.
			<br/>
			The next step is to specify how to generate the key (choose
			characters to extract, algorithms to apply on the column, etc). The
			concatenation of the results of the algorithms will generate a key.
			<br/>
			When complete, click <b>Chart</b> to compute the key on the data sample and show the results in a chart. The
			chart shows how data are partitioned. It is recommended to have the
			size of the partition as small as possible (the horizontal
			coordinate).
		</description>
	</item>
	<item title="Define the Match Rule">
		<description>
			In the match editor, click the &quot;Select Matching Key&quot; button. Then
			click the column header in the data table. Select all
			attributes required to the match operation the same way. In the <b>Matching Key</b> table, choose the algorithms you want to
			apply to the comparison (
			<b>Matching Function</b>
			) and the other match parameters.
			<br/>
			When done, you can visualize the
			result of the configuration applied to the data sample by clicking on
			the
			<b>Chart</b>
			button. Repeat this step until the configuration is satisfying.

		</description>
	</item>
	<item skip="true" title="Export the Match Rule">
		<description>
			Once you test the Match Rule on the sample data and see that it correctly identifies duplicates, you can export it by using the export icon on the toolbar of the match editor then it will show as a <b>Match Rule</b> item in the <b>DQ Repository</b>. You can use the exported Match Rule in other analyses or in Data Quality matching components.
		</description>
		<action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.ExportMatchRuleAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core">
		</action>
	</item>
	<item title="Analyze">
		<description>
			Click the
			<b>Run</b>
			icon on the match editor toolbar to execute the
			analysis on the whole data set. The match editor switches to the <b>Analysis Results</b>
			view showing the matching results on your data.
		</description>
	  <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.RunAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false">
	  </action>

	</item>
</cheatsheet>
