<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet
      title="Create a new nominal correlation analysis">
   <intro>
      <description>
         This type of analysis examines minimal correlations between nominal columns in a particular table and displays the results in a chart. It highlights weak relationships between pairs of data in order to indicate potentially incorrect relationships.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item dialog="true"
         title="Set the analysis metadata">
      <description>
         To open the <b>Create New Analysis</b> wizard,  right click the <b>Analyses</b> folder on the <b>DQ Repository</b> tree view and select <b>New Analysis</b> (or click the link below). Expand <b>Correlation Analysis</b> and select <b>Nominal Correlation Analysis </b>in the wizard. The wizard prompts you to provide the analysis metadata (name, purpose, description....). Upon completion, an editor opens in which you can define the analysis settings.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.CreateNewAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="true" param1="8" param2="1"/>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Select the columns to analyse">
      <description>
         Click the <b>Analyzed Columns</b> to open the corresponding view(or click the link below). Then click <b>Select columns to analyze</b> to open a dialog box in which you can browse to and select the nominal and interval columns to analyze.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.OpenColumnSelectorAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false" param1="8">
      </action>
   </item>
   <item
         skip="true"
         title="Select the right data mining type">
      <description>
         Next to each column, there is a corresponding Data Mining Type box. Select the relevant data mining type from the list.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Analyze">
      <description>
         To execute the analysis, click the <b>Run</b> icon located to the top left of the editor (or click the link below). Alternatively, right click the analysis under the <b>Analyses</b> folder on the <b>DQ Repository</b> tree view and select the Run icon on the context menu.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.RunAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false">
      </action>
   </item>
      <item title="Refresh the graphics" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
       To view the analysis graphics, click the <b>Refresh the graphics</b>  hyperlink (or click the link below). The graphics displayed will reflect the most recently computed data.     
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.RefreshChartAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false" param1="8">
      </action>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
