<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet
      title="Create a new redundancy analysis">
   <intro>
      <description>
          This type of analysis allows you to better examine the quality of data and the relationships between tables by comparing identical columns in different tables or comparing the tables themselves.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item
         skip="false" dialog="true"
         title="Set the analysis metadata">
      <description>
To open the <b>Create New Analysis</b> wizard, right click <b>Analyses</b> on the <b>DQ Repository</b> view and select <b>New Analysis</b>. Then expand <b>Cross Table Analysis</b> and select <b>Redundancy Analysis</b>. The wizard prompts you to provide the analysis metadata (name, purpose, description...). Upon completion, an editor opens in which you can modify the analysis metadata and define the analysis settings.         
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.CreateNewAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false" param1="1"/>
   </item>
   <item dialog="true"
         title="Select columns for set A">
      <description>
         Click <b>Analyzed Column Sets</b> to open the corresponding view (or click the link below). Then click <b>A Column Set</b>. A dialog box opens in which you can browse to and select the first set of columns.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.OpenColumnSelectorAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false" param1="1" param2="0"/>
   </item>
   <item dialog="true"
         title="Select columns for set B">
      <description>
         Click <b>Analyzed Column Sets</b> to open the corresponding view(or click the link below). Then click <b>B Column Set</b>. A dialog box opens in which you can browse to and select the second set of columns.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.OpenColumnSelectorAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false" param1="1" param2="1"/>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Analyze">
      <description>
	  Click the <b>Run</b> icon, located towards the top left of the editor, to execute the analysis. Alternatively, right click the analysis on the <b>DQ Repository</b> tree view and click the <b>Run</b> icon on the list which appears.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.RunAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false"/>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
