<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet
      title="Create a new time correlation analysis">
   <intro>
      <description>
         This type of analysis examines the correlation between nominal and date columns and returns the result in a gantt chart that illustrates the start and finish dates of each variable.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item dialog="true"
         title="Set the analysis metadata">
      <description>
         To open the <b>Create New Analysis</b> wizard, right click the <b>Analyses</b> folder on the <b>DQ Repository</b> tree view and select <b>New Analysis</b>. Browse to and select <b>Time Correlation Analysis</b>. Alternatively, right click a nominal or date column and select <b>Analyze correlation</b> (or click the link below). The wizard prompts you to provide the analysis metadata (name, purpose, description...). Upon completion, an editor opens in which you can define the analysis settings.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.CreateNewAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="true" param1="8" param2="2"/>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Select columns to analyze">
      <description>
         In the editor, click <b> Analyzed Columns</b> (or click the link below). Then click <b>Select columns to analyze</b> to open a dialog box in which you can browse to and select the nominal and date columns to analyze. Alternatively, you can drop the columns from the <b>DQ Repository</b> tree view onto the <b>Analyzed Columns</b> box in the editor.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.OpenColumnSelectorAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false" param1="8">
      </action>
   </item>
   <item
         skip="true"
         title="Select the right data mining type">
      <description>
         Next to each column, there is a corresponding <b>Data Mining Type</b> box. Select the appropriate data mining type from the list.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Analyze">
      <description>
         To execute the analysis, click the <b>Run</b> icon located to the top left of the editor. Alternatively, right click the analysis under the <b>Analyses</b> folder on the <b>DQ Repository</b> view and then select the <b>Run</b> icon (or click the link below).
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.RunAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false">
      </action>
   </item>
      <item title="Refresh the graphics" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
          To generate the analysis graphics, click the <b>Refresh the graphics</b> hyperlink (or click the link below). <b>Refresh the graphics</b> means that the graphics displayed are based on the most recently computed data.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.RefreshChartAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false" param1="8">
      </action>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
