<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet
      title="Create a new columns comprision analysis">
   <intro>
      <description>
          This type of analysis enables you to better explore the quality of data and the relationship between tables through comparing identical columns in tables or comparing tables themselves.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item
         skip="false" dialog="true"
         title="Set the analysis metadata">
      <description>
         This step opens the <b> Create New Analysis </b> wizard. You can <b> right click on the &quot;Analysis&quot; folder or on a column</b> (or <b>click the link below</b>). This wizard helps you to fill the analysis metadata (name, purpose, description....). At the end it opens the corresponding editor in which you can define the settings of the analysis.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.CreateNewAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false" param1="1"/>
   </item>
   <item dialog="true"
         title="Select columns for the A set">
      <description>
         Click the<b> &quot;Analyzed Column Sets&quot;</b> hyperlink (or <b> click the link below</b>). Then click <b> &quot;Select columns for set A&quot;</b> to open a dialog box where you can select the first set of columns.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.OpenColumnSelectorAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false" param1="1" param2="0"/>
   </item>
   <item dialog="true"
         title="Select columns for the B set">
      <description>
         Click the<b> &quot;Analyzed Column Sets&quot;</b> hyperlink (or <b> click the link below</b>). Then click <b> &quot;Select columns for set B&quot;</b> to open a dialog box where you can select the second set of columns.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.OpenColumnSelectorAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false" param1="1" param2="1"/>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Analyze">
      <description>
         To execute the analysis, click on the &quot;Run&quot; button at the bottom of the editor (or click the link below). You can run the analysis with a context menu on the &quot;Analysis&quot; object in the &quot;DQ Repository&quot; view.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.RunAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false"/>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
