<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Create a new column analysis">
   <intro>
      <description>
         <b>This tutorial guides you through the creation of an analysis of the content of a set of columns.</b>
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="Set the analysis metadata." dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         This step opens the analysis creation wizard. It can be open with a <b> right click on the &quot;Analysis&quot; folder or on a column</b>. This wizard helps you to fill the analysis metadata (name, purpose, description....) and then opens an editor in which the settings of the analysis can be filled in.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.CreateNewAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false">
      </action>
   </item>
   <item title="Select the columns to analyze." dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Choose the columns that you want to analyze. If you know the content of a column, set its type to either &quot;Nominal&quot;, or &quot;Interval&quot;. &quot;Nominal&quot; means that the column contains textual values (no order, no mathematical function applicable). On the other hand, &quot;Interval&quot; means that mathematical functions (such as the average) can be used. This type is to be set in the editor.
This window is open when clicking on the<b> &quot;Add columns&quot; button </b>.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.OpenColumnSelectorAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false">
      </action>
   </item>
   <item title="Choose the indicators to compute." dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         For each column, a set of indicators can be selected. These are the indicators to be computed. This window is open when clicking on the <b> &quot;Add indicators&quot; button </b> for a column.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.OpenIndicatorSelectorAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false">
      </action>
   </item>
   <item title="Set the parameters of the indicators." dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Indicators may need some parameters. You can set these parameters by clicking the <b> &quot;options&quot; button </b> for each indicator. By default, reasonable parameters are chosen.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Filter data to analyze." dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Now it&apos;s time to set some filters on the data that you want to analyze. This step is optional. By default, all the data are analyzed. Filters can be written by hand.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Analyze." dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         The analysis can now be executed. Just click on the  <b>&quot;run analysis&quot; button</b>.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.RunAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false">
      </action>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
