<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Create a new column analysis">
   <intro>
      <description>
         This tutorial guides you through the creation of an analysis of the content of a set of columns.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="Set the analysis metadata." dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         This step opens the analysis creation wizard. You can <b> right click on the &quot;Analysis&quot; folder or on a column</b> or click the link below. This wizard helps you to fill the analysis metadata (name, purpose, description....). At the end it opens an editor in which you will define the settings of the analysis.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.CreateNewAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false">
      </action>
   </item>
   <item title="Select the columns to analyze." dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Click on the<b> &quot;Add columns&quot; button</b> or the link below.

If you know the content of a column, set its type to either &quot;Nominal&quot;, or &quot;Interval&quot;. &quot;Nominal&quot; means that the column contains textual values (no order, no mathematical function applicable). On the other hand, &quot;Interval&quot; means that mathematical functions (such as the average) can be used. This type is to be set in the editor.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.OpenColumnSelectorAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false">
      </action>
   </item>
   <item title="Choose the indicators to compute." dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Click on the <b> &quot;Add indicators&quot; button </b> to select a set of indicators to be computed for each column. Or click the link below.
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.OpenIndicatorSelectorAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false">
      </action>
   </item>
   <item title="Set the indicators&apos; options." dialog="true" skip="true">
      <description>
         Click on the <b> &quot;options&quot; button </b> for each indicator you want to set the options. By default, reasonable options are chosen.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Filter data to analyze." dialog="true" skip="true">
      <description>
         This step is optional. By default, all the data are analyzed. 
To filter data, you must write a SQL where clause in the data filter text area.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Analyze." dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         To execute the analysis, click on the  <b>&quot;run analysis&quot; button</b>.
This action can be performed with a context menu on the &quot;Analysis&quot; objects in the &quot;DQ Repository&quot; view
      </description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.RunAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false">
      </action>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
