<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Create a new Match Analysis">
	<intro>
		<description>
			This kind of analysis analyzes duplicate and similar records. It
			helps you define
			<b>Match Rules</b>
			that can be used in analyses or in match components.
		</description>
	</intro>
	<item title="Set the analysis metadata.">
		<description>
			To open the
			<b>Create New Analysis</b>
			wizard, right click
			<b>Analyses</b>
			on the
			<b>DQ Repository</b>
			view and select
			<b>New Analysis</b>
			. Then browse to and select
			<b>Match Analysis</b>
			. The wizard prompts you to provide the analysis metadata (name,
			purpose, description...). Upon completion, an editor opens in which
			you can modify the analysis metadata and define the analysis
			settings.
		</description>
		<action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.CreateNewAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false" param1="12">
        </action>
	</item>
	<item skip="true" title="Connect to a data source">
		<description>
			Create the
			<b>connection</b>
			to the data source to analyze. If you already defined some metadata
			that you want to reuse, just skip this step.
			To create a metadata
			connection, you can click on the
			<b>New Connection</b>
			button in the
			<b>Match Analysis</b>
			editor.
			You can also right-click on the subfolders of the
			<b>Metadata</b>
			folder in the
			<b>DQ Repository view.</b>
			During this step, you will be invited to select the columns to
			analyze.
		</description>
        <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.CreateNewConnectionForMatchAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core">
        </action>
	</item>

	<item skip="true" title="Select data to analyze">
		<description>
			If you already selected the data to analyze in the previous step, you
			may skip this step.
			In the editor, click the &quot;Select Data&quot;
			button. Then browse
			and
			select the
			<b>columns to analyze</b>
		</description>
        <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.SelectDataForMatchAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core">
        </action>
	</item>

	<item title="Generate a blocking key">
		<description>
			Select the columns that will be used to generate a blocking key. A
			blocking key is required when you have a lot of data
			to analyze. Click
			on the
			<b>Select Blocking Key</b>
			button and select the header in the data table to add columns to the
			blocking key section, then click on the
			<b>Select Blocking Key</b> again to finish the selection. Then choose how to generate the key (choose
			characters to extract, algorithms to apply on the column, etc). The
			concatenation of the results of the algorithms will generate a key.
			When complete, you can view the key profile on the data sample. This
			profile shows how data are partitionned. It&apos;s advised that the
			size of the partition is as small as possible (the horizontal
			coordinate).
		</description>
	</item>
	<item title="Define the Match Rule">
		<description>
			In the editor, click the &quot;Select Matching Key&quot; button. Then
			select the columns by clicking in the data table header.
			When all
			attribute required to match are selected, choose the algorithms
			to
			apply for the comparison (
			<b>Match Function</b>
			) and the other match parameters. When done, you can visualize the
			result of the configuration applied to the data sample by clicking on
			the
			<b>Chart</b>
			button. Repeat this step until the configuration is satisfying.

		</description>
	</item>
	<item skip="true" title="Export the Match Rule">
        <description>
            Once the Match Rule correctly identifies duplicates, you can export it as a <b>Match Rule</b> item in the <b>DQ Repository</b>. The exported Match Rule will be reusable in other analyses or in Data Quality matching components.  
        </description>
        <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.ExportMatchRuleAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core">
        </action>
	</item>
	<item title="Analyze">
		<description>
			Click the
			<b>Run</b>
			icon, located towards the top left of the editor, to execute the
			analysis. The
			<b>editor result</b>
			tab will be displayed after the analysis is executed on the whole
			data set.
		</description>
      <action class="org.talend.dataprofiler.core.ui.action.actions.RunAnalysisAction" pluginId="org.talend.dataprofiler.core" confirm="false">
      </action>

	</item>
</cheatsheet>
